Contact

+55 47 99155-4827 (Mobile) email@djonathan.com

www.linkedin.com/in/djonathan-krause-8981a788 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Problem Solving SQL JavaScript

Languages

English (Professional Working)
Portuguese (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

HIGHJUMP UNIVERSITY
Minicurso Básico de Power BI
Duolingo English Fluency: Advanced
(Estimated)

Djonathan Krause

Software Developer at SOCi - Making sure all bugs are dead Blumenau, Santa Catarina, Brazil

Summary

Experience developing within the HighJump/Körber platform utilizing Advantage Architect, WebWise Page Editor. Proficient with relational database development using SQL Server/Oracle.

History working in big projects leading teams and performing code reviews, technical guidance to other developers, and designing process flows (technical/functional).

Experience

SOCi, Inc. Software Engineer April 2022 - Present (3 years 2 months)

In this role I'm working mainly with:

- Bugs solving;
- Issues discovery;
- Mob programming;
- Tech support;
- PHP, SQL and JavaScript;

Körber Supply Chain LATAM

3 years 3 months

Software Developer
January 2020 - April 2022 (2 years 4 months)

Blumenau, Santa Catarina, Brazil

In this role I:

- Led the software engineers team in the largest WMS project in Latin America (2019/2022) with a team of multiple developers;
- Worked on global projects such as OfficeWorks WMS in 2021;
- Managed projects keeping the customer up to date on the project matters;
- Coded and tested using mainly SQL, Architect, and WebWise Page Editor;
- Went live at customers' site;
- Defined WMS functionally and technically;

- Helped to develop new software tools;
- Helped to improve methodology and coding standards;
- Trained new co-workers;

Software Developer

February 2019 - April 2022 (3 years 3 months)

Blumenau, Santa Catarina, Brazil

transpoBrasil Sistemas Software Developer August 2018 - October 2018 (3 months)

Blumenau Area, Brazil

Java Full Stack Developer

Otimis - Körber 3 years 2 months

Software Developer March 2018 - August 2018 (6 months) Blumenau Area, Brazil

Support Analyst

February 2017 - March 2018 (1 year 2 months)

Blumenau Area, Brazil

Working as a Support Analyst I develop bug fixes and tests and analyze new potential errors in the WMS system from reputed companies like AmBev, Renner, Martins, Drogaria Araújo, Wine...

In this position I have to use my skills on Oracle SQL, Microsoft SQL Server and system development to find and fix bugs.

Technical Support

October 2015 - February 2017 (1 year 5 months)

Blumenau Area, Brazil

Working as a Support Technician I help users about doubts and errors in processes of WMS system of renowned companies like AmBev, Renner, Martins, Drogaria Araújo, Wine...

Estágio

July 2015 - October 2015 (4 months)

SENAI/SC - Serviço Nacional de Aprendizagem Industrial IT Technician

December 2014 - June 2015 (7 months)

Education

FURB - Universidade de Blumenau

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science · (2014 - 2018)

Page 3 of 3